{
    "id": "afdcedbff2384a02bad38ba00ac0601b",
    "title": "Easily Confused Words",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Cold weather ............................... my health.",
            "description": "Affect is the verb. Effect is the noun.",
            "answers": [
                "affected",
                "effected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "292c31529af44a06ba80ea985d45a457"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................................... her on her good looks.",
            "description": "To compliment is to praise. ",
            "answers": [
                "complimented",
                "complemented"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88b9bb5ecbbd4361a21b03efbff820dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The salad perfectly ......................................... the main course.",
            "description": "To complement is to complete.",
            "answers": [
                "complimented",
                "complemented"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8411c7308054dd3be26edb9a985ad56"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not very ..................................... so don't share your secrets with her.",
            "description": "Discreet means careful and prudent. ",
            "answers": [
                "discreet",
                "discrete",
                "discreat"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e90fb9432e264b61b06a1fe35ac7f31a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an ........................................ scientist.",
            "description": "Eminent means accomplished. ",
            "answers": [
                "eminent",
                "imminent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf114ca713404cbaada05fe834719097"
        },
        {
            "question": "War is .........................................",
            "description": "If something is imminent it is about to happen.",
            "answers": [
                "eminent",
                "imminent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1063ddb951440ea95f5fa0985c26e0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "All credit cards are .......................................... here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expected",
                "accepted",
                "excepted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d76515b1f5d441780378bb99524b22d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The councilor was accused of ..................................... the funds.",
            "description": "To misuse is to use something in the wrong way.",
            "answers": [
                "disusing",
                "abusing",
                "misusing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "24c8439ee128431cafbf8515f062b756"
        },
        {
            "question": "The exhibition was held in a ..................................... warehouse.",
            "description": "Disused means no longer being used.",
            "answers": [
                "misused",
                "disused",
                "abused"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8d034e6c0fe475dbc820c9972aaa20d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The book is so boring that it is .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "illegible",
                "unreadable"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "344a77351dd9434bb48d9eb7dc3e5263"
        },
        {
            "question": "The prices of essential commodities ......................................... sharply.",
            "description": "Raise is transitive. That means it must have an expressed object. ",
            "answers": [
                "have risen",
                "have raised"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "40364e3c46d1455c8713800c06bedfaf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The long journey was …………………………………...",
            "description": "Exhausting means tiring. ",
            "answers": [
                "exhausting",
                "exhaustive",
                "exhausted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eebc13f460104c9889a7d1f7369c42b2"
        }
    ]
}